https://parallaxcap.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Last updated: May 22, 2018
Parallax Capital Partners LLC, (“we”, “our”, “us”) is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy, sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us.
If you have any requests concerning your personal information or any queries with regard to these practices please contact our data manager via email at privacy@parallaxcap.com.
INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOU
We may collect and process the following personal data about you:
Information that you provide directly via our website, for example a request for information
Information that you provide when you enter a competition or promotion sponsored by us or third parties, and when you report any problem with our website
If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence, including any phone number or email address you use
Information that you provide when completing surveys that we use for research purposes
Details of your usage of our website including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, logs, error and crash reporting, and other communication data and the resources that you access
Information from any social network or other online accounts that you choose to share with us
USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
We process personal information for the purposes of:
Providing you with our services
Monitoring, analyzing and improving those services
Prevention of money-laundering, fraud & illegal activities, and the prosecution of offenders
Direct-marketing of our products and services, advising you of news and industry updates, events, promotions and competitions, reports and other information and carrying out market research campaigns
Providing you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes
MARKETING
We will not share identifiable personal data with third parties for the purposes of direct marketing without your explicit consent.
We may use and disclose information in aggregate (so that no individuals are identified) for marketing and strategic development purposes.
USE OF COOKIES
In order to improve the website, we may use small files commonly known as “cookies”. A cookie is a small amount of data which often includes a unique identifier that is sent to your computer or mobile phone (referred to in this policy as a ‘device’) from the website and is stored on your device’s hard drive. Our use of cookies also allows certain users to be presented with a personalized version of the site.
We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system information and to report aggregate information. This is statistical data about our users’ browsing actions and patterns and does not identify any individual.
For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. We use cookies to identify you when you visit this website, keep track of your browsing patterns. They help us to improve our website and deliver a better and more personalized service.
If you don’t want us to use cookies when you use the website, you can adjust your internet browser settings not to accept cookies. Your web browser’s help function should tell you how to do this.
Alternatively, you can find information about how to do this for all the commonly used internet browsers on the website: www.aboutcookies.org, it also explains how you can delete cookies which are already stored on your device. Please note however that turning off cookies will restrict your use of our website.
By continuing to use this website you are agreeing to the use of cookies as detailed above.
WHERE WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL DATA
The data we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or one of our suppliers. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.
DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION
We will only disclose data when obliged to disclose personal data by law, or the disclosure is ‘necessary’ for purposes of national security, taxation and criminal investigation, or we have your consent, and to the following:
Other companies within our Group of companies
Business partners
Suppliers we engage to process data on our behalf
Successors in title to our business
ACCESS TO INFORMATION
You have a right to access the personal data held about you or to obtain a copy of it. We may ask you to verify your identity and for more information about your request. To obtain a copy of the personal information we hold about you, please email privacy@parallaxcap.com. Alternatively you can write to us at Parallax Capital Partners, 23332 Mill Creek Dr., Suite 155, Laguna Hills, CA 92653.
AMENDMENTS
Please note that this Privacy Policy is subject to change from time to time. It was last updated on the date shown at the top of this webpage.
This defines our ability to look at a company from various perspectives and to see each potential business acquisition from all angles. This approach, which combines our wealth of experience and proven management capabilities, gives Parallax the capacity to understand a company's current position and the vision to transform the organization to greater success in a changing business environment
Copyright ©2018. All rights reserved.
We use cookies to analyze traffic and ensure that we give you the best experience on our websiteOkPrivacy Policy
